{
  "joke.aow": [
    {
      "question": "Why did Poseidon and Selene break up?",
      "answer": "Because their relationship is *Poselene* (porcelain)",
      "credit": "Kitsune"
    },
    {
      "question": "What hero is really bad at basketball?",
      "answer": "Aly, because she keeps dropping the ball",
      "credit": "Kitsune"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do mages skip school?",
      "answer": "Because they don't want to become scholars.",
      "credit": "Kitsune"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you summon Azrael",
      "answer": "With **nun**-stopping praying",
      "credit": "Kitsune"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the most self-centered hero?",
      "answer": "Chi**one**",
      "credit": "Kitsune"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who won the AoW beauty pageant contest?",
      "answer": "Selene. She was just stunning.",
      "credit": "Harmless Buns"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why were Goblikazes booed off the stage in the concert?",
      "answer": "They totally bombed",
      "credit": "Harmless Buns"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why was Zeus fired as a lifeguard?",
      "answer": "Electricity and water don't mix.",
      "credit": "Harmless Buns"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why is Rhino Knight's credit score so low?",
      "answer": "He keeps charging.",
      "credit": "Harmless Buns"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why was Ivan banned from the zoo?",
      "answer": "He kept chasing the squirrels.",
      "credit": "Harmless Buns"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why is Beast Master terrible at math?",
      "answer": "He got the Axe but not the Whys",
      "credit": "Kitsune"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why won't dev buff Cactuses?",
      "answer": "The problem is too prickly to handle.",
      "credit": "Kitsune"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why isn't Hohenheim a legendary hero?",
      "answer": "Because he can't create gems with alchemy.",
      "credit": "Kitsune"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who got banned from Discord by Ogre Warrior?",
      "answer": "Voodoo Dolls because they kept cursing.",
      "credit": "Kitsune"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why is kriss bad at farming?",
      "answer": "'Cuz Hoheheim got all the hoes.",
      "credit": "Kitsune"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which hero is both sacred and wild?",
      "answer": "Zoos",
      "credit": "Kitsune"
    },
    {
      "question": "Is Planck a Greek hero?",
      "answer": "Well... he sure uses a lot of *greece*",
      "credit": "Kitsune"
    },
    {
      "question": "What was Green like when he was a baby?",
      "answer": "He was an Infantry (infant tree)",
      "credit": "Harmless Buns"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do Davison and Cactuses stack well in battle?",
      "answer": "Dunno. But Cactuses sure stuck to Davison after his dive.",
      "credit": "Kitsune"
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of shoes does Seondeok wear?",
      "answer": "Heels (heals)",
      "credit": "Harmless Buns"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Goblin Tech's favorite classical music?",
      "answer": "Canon (cannon) in D",
      "credit": "Harmless Buns"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do cellists hate Goblin Tech?",
      "answer": "They are reminded of Canon in D",
      "credit": "Kitsune"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which hero is the best deal?",
      "answer": "Charon. He's always on *sail*.",
      "credit": "Kitsune"
    },
    {
      "question": "Real troops never abandon their post.",
      "answer": "How 'bout a boat?",
      "credit": "Kitsune"
    },
    {
      "question": "what is Kraken's favorite TV drama?",
      "answer": "Squid Game.",
      "credit": "Harmless Buns"
    },
    {
      "joke<text>": [
        "One day, Ivan stormed into the developer's meeting and demanded buff to his skills",
        "",
        "The room was in total *silence*..."
      ],
      "credit": "Kitsune"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why did the Peltasts lose the marathon?",
      "answer": "They kept running backwards.",
      "credit": "Harmless Buns"
    },
    {
      "joke<text>": [
        "Aly was strolling in the woods when Miller suddenly stood up from a bush.",
        "Miller eyed Aly's tails and curiously asked “say, do your tails get sticky when you poo?”",
        "“Not at all,” Aly grinned.",
        "“Good!” Miller answered and grabbed one of Aly's tails to wipe his butt."
      ],
      "credit": "Jolihi Kan"
    },
    {
      "question": "If Zeus and Kraken competed in Olympics swimming, who would win?",
      "answer": "Neither, because Kraken won't survive in fresh water, and Zeus would electrocute himself.",
      "credit": "Harmless Buns"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Meteor Golem's favorite band?",
      "answer": "Rolling Stones",
      "credit": "Harmless Buns"
    }
  ]
}
